Master,
يتقن،
the spicy fruit in the stockade,
الفاكهة الحارة في الحاجز ،
All of them have moved here.
كلهم انتقلوا إلى هنا.
Thank you for your hard work.
شكرا لعملكم الشاق.
I don't have enough chilies in the kitchen,
ليس لدي ما يكفي من الفلفل الحار في المطبخ ،
but it finally comes in handy this time.
لكنه أصبح في متناول اليد أخيرًا هذه المرة.
Master,
يتقن،
I didn't expect that you're good at cooking.
لم أكن أتوقع أنك جيد في الطبخ.
Of course.
بالطبع.
We've finally got the silver.
لقد حصلنا أخيرًا على الميدالية الفضية.
Let's redeem the Liu Army now.
دعونا نفدي جيش ليو الآن.
Official Du,
أنت مسؤول ،
the seven-day appointment has arrived.
لقد وصل موعد السبعة أيام.
This is 4. 2 thousand silver,
هذا 4. 2 ألف فضة.
plus the previous deposit,
بالإضافة إلى الإيداع السابق ،
That comes to 5. 2 thousand,
هذا يصل إلى 5. 2 ألف ،
Okay,
تمام،
I, Du Mao, stand by my words,
أنا ، دو ماو ، أقف بجانب كلماتي ،
this 5. 2 thousand,
هذا 5. 2 آلاف ،
Take it as compensation for your trouble
اعتبرها كتعويض عن مشكلتك
in Deciduous City.
في المدينة المتساقطة.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
I'd like to ask,
أود أن أسأل ،
if you come to my Falling Leaf City,
إذا أتيت إلى My Falling Leaf City ،
What do you mean by ruining Jianghe Tower?
ماذا تقصد بتدمير برج جيانغي؟
The boss behind Jianghe House is Du Mao,
الرئيس وراء منزل Jianghe هو Du Mao ،
Okay,
تمام،
Then let's get lost.
ثم دعونا نضيع.
Because he wanted to save the Liu Army,
لأنه أراد إنقاذ جيش ليو ،
he ran Lake Fishing,
كان يدير بحيرة صيد السمك ،
and offended Jianghe House,
وأساء إلى منزل Jianghe ،
The owner of Jianghe House is Du Mao?
مالك منزل Jianghe هو Du Mao؟
If you offend Du Mao,
إذا أساءت إلى دو ماو ،
you won't be able to save the Liu Army.
لن تكون قادرًا على إنقاذ جيش Liu.
We can't save the Liu Army
لا يمكننا إنقاذ جيش ليو
just to save them.
فقط لإنقاذهم.
God's will,
إرادة الله،
stop!
قف!
You even want to take it away.
أنت حتى تريد أن تأخذها بعيدا.
Come on,
تعال،
run!
يجري!
Gosh.
يا الهي.
I'll lose if I lose.
سأخسر إذا خسرت.
Why should I drown my sorrows in alcohol?
لماذا يجب أن أغرق أحزاني في الكحول؟
Pretend to be drunk
يتظاهر بالسكر
and escape from reality.
والهروب من الواقع.
Very happy.
سعيد جدا.
It's been a long time since I had such a good time.
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن قضيت مثل هذا الوقت الجيد.
He,
هو،
Watch out!
احترس!
No!
لا!
It's gone.
لقد ذهب.
5. 2 Thousand is gone.
5. ذهب 2 ألف.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Master,
يتقن،
what should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
This shop is open too.
هذا المحل مفتوح أيضا.
I've earned money.
لقد ربحت المال.
The Liu Family Army hasn't been rescued yet.
لم يتم إنقاذ جيش عائلة ليو بعد.
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
You did your best.
فعلت افضل ما لديكم.
A sad young man.
شاب حزين.
Congratulations on your mission
مبروك على مهمتك
to save the restaurant.
لإنقاذ المطعم.
Reward one chance to draw a warrior.
كافئ فرصة واحدة لرسم محارب.
God is helping me.
الله يساعدني.
Ah,
آه،
Why did you pick a foreign warrior?
لماذا اخترت محاربًا أجنبيًا؟
I wish I could stay drunk for a long time.
أتمنى أن أبقى في حالة سكر لفترة طويلة.
I'll share my sorrow with you forever.
سوف أشاركك حزني إلى الأبد.
Sir,
سيد،
two more pots of good wine.
إناءان آخران من النبيذ الجيد.
His combat strength is only five.
قوته القتالية هي خمسة فقط.
Why did he pick such a loser?
لماذا اختار مثل هذا الخاسر؟
Good wine.
نبيذ جيد.
Again,
مرة أخرى،